Inventory of the Citizens for Reagan Records
Hoover Institution Archives
- Audio-video campaign materials, 1975-1976 (Folder On shelf)
  - 30-60 second statements on 2 inch videotapes (Folder On shelf)
    - Unemployment, 1976 January 22, 60 seconds, 1 videotape (Folder On shelf)
      The 60 second version of this campaign ad (part 1) begins with an unidentified audience member asking Reagan, at the podium, what Reagan would do to reduce the persistent 8 percent unemployment. Reagan replies the elimination of inflation is the only answer. In the 30 second version (part 2), an audience member identifies himself and asks Reagan for his plan for full employment. Reagan replies that ending deficit spending and balancing the budget is the answer. These television commercials for the 1976 Ronald Reagan presidential campaign aired around January 22, 1976.
      Sequence: PART 1 (60 second version): Slate (00:44), man asks question (00:53), Reagan replies (01:06). PART 2 (30 second version): Slate (00:50), man asks question (01:04), Reagan replies (01:14).
    - American People, 1976 January 30, 30 seconds, 9 videotapes (Folder On shelf)
    - Confidence, 1976 January 30, 60 seconds, 8 videotapes (Folder On shelf)
    - Foreign Aid, 1976 January 30, 60 seconds, 9 videotapes (Folder On shelf)
    - Inflation, 1976 January 30, 30 seconds, 11 videotapes (Folder On shelf)
    - Social Security, 1976 January 30, 30 seconds, 18 videotapes (Folder On shelf)
    - Spending, 1976 January 30, 30 seconds, 11 videotapes (Folder On shelf)
    - Unemployment, 1976 January 30, 60 seconds, 10 videotapes (Folder On shelf)
    - Social Security, 1976 February 3, 60 seconds, 3 videotapes (Folder On shelf)
    - Unemployment, 1976 February 3, 60 seconds, 1 videotape (Folder On shelf)
    - The Record, 1976 February 5, 60 seconds, 2 videotapes (Folder On shelf)
    - Defense, 1976 February 10, 30 seconds, 14 videotapes (Folder On shelf)
    - Government, 1976 February 10, 60 seconds, 12 videotapes (Folder On shelf)
    - Inflation, 1976 February 2, 30 seconds, 11 videotapes (Folder On shelf)
    - The Record, 1976 February 2, 60 seconds, 13 videotapes (Folder On shelf)
    - Spending, 1976 February 2, 30 seconds, 11 videotapes (Folder On shelf)
    - Social Security, 1976 February 2, 60 seconds, 13 videotapes (Folder On shelf)
    - Unemployment, 1976 February 2, 60 seconds, 1 videotape (Folder On shelf)
    - Change, 1976 February 11, 30 seconds, 1 videotape (Folder On shelf)
      This ad shows Reagan speaking before an audience, telling them that he believes people from outside Washington must go to work to reverse the nation's course. This television commercial for the 1976 Ronald Reagan presidential campaign aired around February 11, 1976.
      Sequence: Slate (00:40), opens to Reagan speaking to an audience (00:49).
    - People, 1976 February 11, 30 seconds, 1 videotape (Folder On shelf)
      This commercial opens to an audience listening to Ronald Reagan, who is speaking from a podium. Reagan calls for a government that has faith in the people and the people's capacity for greatness; government must be confident in what people can do for themselves. This television commercial for the 1976 Ronald Reagan presidential campaign aired around February 11, 1976.
      Sequence: Slate (01:28), opens to audience listening to Reagan (01:37).
    - Change, 1976 February 13, 30 seconds, 9 videotapes (Folder On shelf)
    - People, 1976 February 13, 30 seconds, 11 videotapes (Folder On shelf)
    - The Record, 1976 February 13, 60 seconds, 8 videotapes (Folder On shelf)
    - Inflation, 1976 February 17, 30 seconds, 1 videotape (Folder On shelf)
    - Spending, 1976 February 17, 30 seconds, 1 videotape (Folder On shelf)
    - Inflation, 1976 February 17, 30 seconds, 1 videotape (Folder On shelf)
    - Bureaucracy, 1976 February 18, 30 seconds, 1 videotape (Folder On shelf)
      Speaking from a podium, Reagan calls for the forced busing of the Washington bureaucracy out to the country, causing the audience to break into applause. This television commercial for the 1976 Ronald Reagan presidential campaign aired around February 18, 1976.
      Sequence: Slate (01:08), opening shot of Reagan at podium (01:17).
    - Change, 1976 February 18, 30 seconds, 18 videotapes (Folder On shelf)
      Conditions Governing Access note
      Use copy reference number: 81141_v_0001517
    - Defense, 1976 February 18, 30 seconds, 1 videotape (Folder On shelf)
    - People, 1976 February 18, 30 seconds, 16 videotapes (Folder On shelf)
    - The Record, 1976 February 18, 60 seconds, 3 videotapes (Folder On shelf)
    - Social Security, 1976 February 18, 60 seconds, 3 videotapes (Folder On shelf)
    - Spending, 1976 February 18, 30 seconds, 3 videotape (Folder On shelf)
    - Taxes, 1976 February 18, 30 seconds, 15 videotape (Folder On shelf)
    - Unemployment, 1976 February 18, 60 seconds, 17 videotape (Folder On shelf)
    - American People, 1976 February 19, 30 seconds, 1 videotape (Folder On shelf)
    - Bureaucracy, 1976 February 19, 30 seconds, 5 videotape (Folder On shelf)
    - Change, 1976 February 19, 30 seconds, 6 videotape (Folder On shelf)
    - Defense, 1976 February 19, 30 seconds, 8 videotape (Folder On shelf)
    - Government, 1976 February 19, 60 seconds, 10 videotape (Folder On shelf)
    - Inflation, 1976 February 19, 30 seconds, 9 videotape (Folder On shelf)
    - People, 1976 February 19, 30 seconds, 8 videotape (Folder On shelf)
    - The Record, 1976 February 19, 60 seconds, 5 videotape (Folder On shelf)
    - Social Security, 1976 February 19, 60 seconds, 6 videotape (Folder On shelf)
    - Spending, 1976 February 19, 30 seconds, 7 videotape (Folder On shelf)
    - Taxes, 1976 February 19, 30 seconds, 7 videotape (Folder On shelf)
    - Unemployment, 1976 February 19, 60 seconds, 5 videotape (Folder On shelf)
    - Spending, 1976 February 20, 30 seconds, 1 videotape (Folder On shelf)
    - The Record, 1976 February 24, 30 seconds, 1 videotape (Folder On shelf)
    - Spending, 1976 February 24, 30 seconds, 1 videotape (Folder On shelf)
    - Change, 1976 February 27, 30 seconds, 1 videotape (Folder On shelf)
    - Defense, 1976 February 27, 30 seconds, 1 videotape (Folder On shelf)
    - Government, 1976 February 27, 60 seconds, 1 videotape (Folder On shelf)
    - Inflation, 1976 February 27, 30 seconds, 1 videotape (Folder On shelf)
    - People, 1976 February 27, 30 seconds, 1 videotape (Folder On shelf)
    - The Record, 1976 February 27, 60 seconds, 1 videotape (Folder On shelf)
    - Social security, 1976 February 27, 60 seconds, 1 videotape (Folder On shelf)
    - Spending, 1976 February 27, 30 seconds, 1 videotape (Folder On shelf)
    - Taxes, 1976 February 27, 30 seconds, 1 videotape (Folder On shelf)
    - Governor, 1976 March 1, 30 seconds, 10 videotape (Folder On shelf)
    - Leadership, 1976 March 1, 60 seconds, 10 videotape (Folder On shelf)
    - Winner, 1976 March 1, 30 seconds, 11 videotape (Folder On shelf)
    - Detente, 1976 March 2, 30 seconds, 10 videotape (Folder On shelf)
    - Panama, 1976 March 2, 30 seconds, 6 videotape (Folder On shelf)
      This ad opens to Reagan at the podium of an event at the Wilmington Hilton. He declares that the Canal Zone is US territory, asserting that it is essential to Western Hemisphere defense and that the world is safer with the US operating the canal. This television commercial for the 1976 Ronald Reagan presidential campaign aired around March 2, 1976.
      Sequence: Slate (00:52), open to Reagan at podium (01:03).
    - Strength, 1976 March 2, 30 seconds, 10 videotape (Folder On shelf)
    - Government, 1976 March 3, 60 seconds, 1 videotape (Folder On shelf)
    - Panama, 1976 March 3, 30 seconds, 1 videotape (Folder On shelf)
    - The Record, 1976 March 3, 60 seconds, 1 videotape (Folder On shelf)
    - Detente, 1976 March 8, 30 seconds, 15 videotape (Folder On shelf)
    - Governor, 1976 March 8, 30 seconds, 2 videotape (Folder On shelf)
    - Leadership, 1976 March 8, 60 seconds, 16 videotape (Folder On shelf)
    - Strength, 1976 March 8, 30 seconds, 15 videotape (Folder On shelf)
    - Winner, 1976 March 8, 30 seconds, 15 videotape (Folder On shelf)
    - Governor, 1976 March 9, 30 seconds, 16 videotape (Folder On shelf)
    - No Time, 1976 March 13, 60 seconds, 11 videotapes (Folder On shelf)
    - Winner, 1976 March 13, 30 seconds, 9 videotape (Folder On shelf)
    - Reagan/Rep. For President, 1976 March 20, 30 seconds 1 videotape (Folder On shelf)
    - Ronald Reagan: RR 632 "I Believe", RR 633 "No Time", 1976 April 14, 30 seconds, 7 videotape (Folder On shelf)
    - Ronald Reagan: RR 634, RR 636R, 1976 April 16, 30 seconds, 7 videotape (Folder On shelf)
    - Ronald Reagan: RR 634, RR 635, RR 636R, 1976 April 16, 30 seconds, 2 videotape (Folder On shelf)
    - Ronald Reagan: RR 632 "I Believe", 1976 April 17, 30 seconds, 1 videotape (Folder On shelf)
    - Ronald Reagan: RR 661, RR 662, 1976 April 27, 60 seconds, 1 videotape (Folder On shelf)
    - Ronald Reagan: 6 spots tied, 1976 May 5, 30 seconds, 1 videotape (Folder On shelf)
    - Ronald Reagan Comm'l Reel: "Little Girl", "Sure Way" "Social Security", 60 seconds, 28 April 1976, 1 videotape (Folder On shelf)
      These three campaign ads feature Ronald Reagan sitting in a chair in what appears to be a living room. They were taped on April 27, 1976.
      In "Little Girl," Reagan talks about the question a little girl asked him about why he wanted to be president. He tried to answer her, but did not realize until later what he should have said. Reagan wished he had told her that he wants to see if he can "make this country again as free for a little six year old to grow up in as it was when I was six years old growing up in America."
      The "Sure Way" ad is very short; the entirety is Reagan saying, "The one sure way to guarantee world peace is to restore our defense superiority. That's real peace through strength."
      In "Social Security," Reagan explains how he differs from Gerald Ford on social security. Ford wants to preserve the integrity of social security, whereas Reagan wants to restore its integrity.
      Sequence: Little Girl slate (00:29), opens to Reagan (00:48), Reagan closing message (01:41), black (01:50), Sure Way slate (01:58), opens to Reagan (02:18), Reagan closing message (02:26), Social Security slate (02:39), opens to Reagan (02:59), Reagan closing message (03:54).
    - Reagan for President, "Dealer Plug", 30 seconds, 29 April 1976, 1 videotape (Folder On shelf)
    - Reagan for President, "Glasses", 30 seconds, 29 April 1976, 1 videotape (Folder On shelf)
      - 5-60 minute statements on 2 inch videotape (Folder On shelf)
        - Reagan, 1976 March 16, 30 minutes, 1 reel (Folder On shelf)
          In this video recording Reagan speaks while sitting at a desk in a staged setting. Reagan discusses his disagreements with policies of the Gerald Ford administration. He concludes by stating he wants to go to Washington so that he can "see this country become once again ... the kind of country--the free country--that you and I grew up in."
          Sequence: slates (00:51), Reagan begins speaking (01:13), Reagan concludes, closing slate (28:10), black (28:20).
        - Ronald Reagan Address, 1976 March 31, 1 reel (Folder On shelf)
        - POL.TALK Ronald Reagan, 1976 April 12, 1 reel (Folder On shelf)
        - Texas Citizens for Reagan, 1976 April 15, 28 minutes 45 seconds, 2 reel (Folder On shelf)
        - Reagan 30 Minute Program, 1976 April 21, 30 minutes, 5 reels (Folder On shelf)
        - Reagan 30 Minute Program, 1976 May 1, 30 minutes, 1 reel (Folder On shelf)
        - Political Talk: Citizens for Ronald Reagan, 1976 May 5, 30 minutes, 1 reel (Folder On shelf)
        - Reagan, 1976 May 19, 20 minutes 33 seconds, 1 reel (Folder On shelf)
        - Reagan's Speech, 1976 March 31, 30 minutes, 2 reel (Folder On shelf)
    - Tape Films Reveal, "Vegetables", 30 seconds, 29 April 1976, 1 videotape (Folder On shelf)
    - Reagan Spot, "Micromedia", 30 seconds, 1 videotape (Folder On shelf)
    - Jimmy Stewart, 1976 March 19, 3 videotapes (Folder On shelf)
  - 1-5 minute statements on 2 inch videotape (Folder On shelf)
    - The Reagan Story, 1976 February 12, 4:28, 5 videotapes (Folder On shelf)
    - The Reagan Story, 1976 February 17, 4:30, 7 videotapes (Folder On shelf)
    - The Reagan Story, 1976 February 19, 4:30, 1 videotape (Folder On shelf)
    - The Reagan Story, 1976 February 27, 5:00 1 videotape (Folder On shelf)
    - Ronald Reagan, "Foreign Policy," 1976 March 9, 5:00, 5 videotape (Folder On shelf)
      In a staged setting without an audience, Reagan talks at a podium about security and defense issues, which he believes are beyond politics. The Soviets are ahead of the US in the arms race, and the Ford and Kissinger leadership must be held accountable. The "delusions of detente" are contradictory with a genuine peace, and the Ford/Kissinger peace is a "peace of the grave."
      Sequence: Slate (00:44), "Reagan" title and voice-over (00:56), Reagan begins (01:02), "Reagan" title and voice-over (05:24), black (05:32).
    - Ronald Reagan "Busing", 1976 March 13, 57 seconds, 2 videotapes (Folder On shelf)
    - Reagan news conference opening statement dub, 1976 March 13, 1 minute 49 seconds, 2 videotapes (Folder On shelf)
    - Reagan for President, 1976 April 29, 4 minutes 30 seconds, 4 videotape (Folder On shelf)
    - Helms for Reagan, 4:45 seconds, 2 videotape (Folder On shelf)
    - Statement by Ronald Reagan for Release, 1976, March 4, 8 videotapes (Folder On shelf)
  - 30 and 60 second statements on 1 inch video tape (Folder On shelf)
  - 12 phonodiscs (records) with 30 minute statements (Folder On shelf)
    - Nationally televised "NBC" 30-minute address, 31 March 1976
      Access
      Use copy reference number: 81141_a_0008933
      Campaigning for the Republican nomination for president in 1976, Reagan criticizes the Ford administration on a variety of issues, domestic and foreign.
  - 1/4 inch sound recording reels (Folder On shelf)
    - Eight radio spots, 1.0 sound tape reel (Folder On shelf)
      Pain of Inflation, 31 seconds, California Record, 27 seconds, Foreign Policy, 31 seconds, Unemployment, 58 seconds, Energy, 50 seconds, Welfare Reform, 59 seconds, Détente, 59 seconds, Our Destiny, 60 seconds. Use copy reference number: 81141_a_0009221
    - Three radio spots (Folder On shelf)
      Little Girl, 60 seconds, Social Security, 60 seconds, Five-Minute message. Use copy reference number: 81141_a_0009222
  - Compact sound cassettes (phonotapes), 1970-1980, undated. (Box 112-120)
    502 tapes.
    - 1976 Campaign audio recordings (Tape 112-119)
      - January 5 (Tape 112: 1)
        Use copy reference number: 81141_a_0013141
      - January 5-6 (Tape 112: 2)
      - January 6 (Tape 112: 3)
      - January 6-7 (Tape 112: 4)
      - January 7-8 (Tape 112: 5)
      - January 8 (Tape 112: 6)
      - Press Conference, January 9 (Tape 112: 7)
      - January 10 (Tape 112: 8)
      - January 12 (Tape 112: 9)
      - Springfield/Bloomington, January 12 (Tape 112: 10)
      - January 13 (Tape 112: 11)
      - January 15 (Tape 112: 12)
      - January 15-16 (Tape 112: 13)
      - January 16 (Tape 112: 14-15)
      - Angola, January 17 (Tape 112: 16)
      - January 26 (Tape 112: 17-18)
      - master copy, January 26-27 (Tape 112: 19)
      - Panama City, Florida, January 26-27 (Tape 112: 20)
      - Ashville/Gastonia, North Carolina, January 27-28 (Tape 112: 21)
      - Master copy: Asheville, North Carolina/Manchester New Hampshire, January 27-28 (Tape 112: 22)
      - Asheville, North Carolina/Manchester New Hampshire, January 27-28 (Tape 112: 23)
      - January 28 (Tape 112: 24)
      - Night Speech, January 28 (Tape 112: 25)
      - January 29 (Tape 112: 26)
      - January 29 (Tape 112: 27)
      - Rod Paul, January 29 (Tape 112: 28)
      - January 29 (Tape 112: 29)
      - January 30 (Tape 112: 30-31)
      - February 1 (Tape 112: 32)
      - February 3-4 (Tape 112: 33)
      - Fort Lauderdale, February 4 (Tape 112: 34)
      - February 4 (Tape 112: 35)
      - February 4-5 (Tape 112: 36)
      - February 5 (Tape 112: 37)
      - February 5 (Tape 113: 1-3)
      - February 6 (Tape 113: 4)
      - February 6-7 (Tape 113: 5)
      - February 7 (Tape 113: 6-8)
      - February 9 (Tape 113: 9-10)
      - February 9-10 (Tape 113: 11)
      - February 10 (Tape 113: 12-15)
      - February 11 (Tape 113: 16)
      - New York speech, February 11 (Tape 113: 17)
      - February 12 (Tape 113: 18)
      - 15 minute, February 12 (Tape 113: 19)
      - February 12 (Tape 113: 20)
      - master copy, February 13 (Tape 113: 21)
      - February 13 (Tape 113: 22)
      - master copy, press conference, February 13 (Tape 113: 23)
      - Press conference continued, February 13 (Tape 113: 24)
      - February 13 (Tape 113: 25)
      - February 13-14 (Tape 113: 26)
      - February 14 (Tape 113: 27)
      - Disney World Speech, February 14-15 (Tape 113: 28)
      - Night speeches/press conference, February 20 (Tape 113: 29)
      - February 21 (Tape 113: 30-32)
      - February 22 (Tape 113: 33)
      - February 23 (Tape 113: 34-35)
      - Manchester, February 24 (Tape 113: 36)
      - Election Press Conference, February 24-25 (Tape 114: 1)
      - February 25-26 (Tape 114: 2)
      - February 26 (Tape 114: 3)
      - February 27 (Tape 114: 4-6)
      - February 28 (Tape 114: 7)
      - February 28, March 4 (Tape 114: 8)
      - March 5 (Tape 114: 9-11)
      - March 6 (Tape 114: 12-13)
      - Meet the Press, March 7 (Tape 114: 14)
      - Cubans/West Palm Beach, March 7 (Tape 114: 15)
      - Press Conference, March 8 (Tape 114: 16)
      - March 8 (Tape 114: 17)
      - March 9 (Tape 114: 18)
      - March 9-10 (Tape 114: 19)
      - March 10 (Tape 114: 20-21)
      - March 10-11 (Tape 114: 22)
      - Press Conference, March 11 (Tape 114: 23)
      - March 11-12 (Tape 114: 24)
      - Master copy, March 12 (Tape 114: 25)
      - March 12 (Tape 114: 26-27)
      - Press conference, Chicago, March 12-13 (Tape 114: 28)
      - Press conference, Springfield, March 13 (Tape 114: 29)
      - March 17-18 (Tape 114: 30)
      - March 18 (Tape 114: 31)
      - Interviews, March 18 (Tape 114: 32)
      - Interview, March 18-19 (Tape 114: 33)
      - Interview, Charlotte, North Carolina, March 19 (Tape 114: 34)
      - March 19 (Tape 114: 35)
      - Radio interviews/Ashville, North Carolina Rally March 19 (Tape 114: 36)
      - Ashbury, North Carolina March 20 (Tape 114: 37)
      - Green Bay television interviews/Press Conference March 22 (Tape 115: 1)
      - March 22-23 (Tape 115: 2)
      - March 23 (Tape 115: 3-4)
      - Richmond Trip, March 27 (Tape 115: 5)
      - Speech, March 27 (Tape 115: 6-8)
      - Ronald Reagan Address, March 31 (Tape 115: 9-24)
      - Press conference, April 2 (Tape 115: 25)
      - Dallas Press Conference, April 5 (Tape 115: 26)
      - April 5 (Tape 115: 27)
      - Master copy: Wichita Falls/SMU Dallas, April 6 (Tape 115: 28)
      - Wichita Falls/SMU Dallas, April 6 (Tape 115: 29)
      - Private interviews: Abilene April 6 (Tape 115: 30)
      - Master copy: Lubbock speech, April 6 (Tape 115: 31)
      - End Abilene speech/Lubbock, April 6 (Tape 115: 32)
      - Wisconsin statement, Longview, Texas, April 6-7 (Tape 115: 33)
      - Longview, Salt Lake City, April 7 (Tape 115: 34)
      - Phoenix; Denver, April 8 (Tape 115: 35)
      - Arizona, Cheyenne, Wyoming, April 8-9 (Tape 115: 36)
      - Cheyenne, Wyoming, April 9 (Tape 115: 37)
      - Seattle press conference, interview, April 10 (Tape 115: 38)
      - Seattle, Reagan in LA, Texas, April 10, 12-13 (Tape 116: 1)
      - Texas, Austin Press Conference, April 13-14 (Tape 116: 2)
      - April 14 (Tape 116: 3-4)
      - Master copy: Houston, Texas, April 15 (Tape 116: 5)
      - Houston, Texas, April 15 (Tape 116: 6)
      - April 15 (Tape 116: 7-8)
      - New Mexico, April 20 (Tape 116: 9)
      - CBS, Macon, Augusta, April 20-21 (Tape 116: 10)
      - Master copy: WJBF TV, Augusta and Savannah, Georgia, April 21 (Tape 116: 11)
      - WJBF TV, Augusta and Savannah, Georgia, April 21 (Tape 116: 12)
      - Savannah rally, Mobile Alabama, WALA TV interview, April 22 (Tape 116: 13)
      - Mobile, Montgomery, Panama, April 22 (Tape 116: 14)
      - Clinton, Alabama, April 22 (Tape 116: 15)
      - Indianapolis TV interview, April 23 (Tape 116: 16)
      - TV speech, Fort Wayne, Indiana, April 23 (Tape 116: 17)
      - Evansville; Indianapolis; April 27 (Tape 116: 18)
      - Anderson, Indiana; Albany, Georgia; Columbus, April 28 (Tape 116: 19)
      - Atlanta press conference; Columbus; Georgia, April 28 (Tape 116: 20)
      - Huntsville; Atlanta, April 28-29 (Tape 116: 21)
      - Radio interview, April 29 (Tape 116: 22)
      - Master copy: interview, April 29 (Tape 116: 23)
      - Tyler, Texas, April 29 (Tape 116: 24)
      - Huntsville TV interview; Houston rally, April 29 (Tape 116: 25)
      - Beaumont, Texas; the Alamo, San Antonio, April 30 (Tape 116: 26)
      - San Antonio, April 30 (Tape 116: 27)
      - Interview WAKO; Dallas, Texas, April 30 (Tape 116: 28)
      - Texas; Hammond, Indiana, April 30-May 1 (Tape 116: 29)
      - Indiana, May 1 (Tape 116: 30)
      - Press conference; Indiana; Fort Wayne, May 2-3 (Tape 116: 31)
      - May 3 (Tape 116: 32)
      - West Virginia, May 4 (Tape 116: 33)
      - Webras, KA; Charleston, West Virginia; Omaha, Nebraska, May 4 (Tape 116: 34)
      - Charleston, West Virginia; Omaha, Nebraska, May 4 (Tape 116: 35)
      - Lincoln networks election night, May 4-5 (Tape 116: 36)
      - LA Times Interview; Webras, Kansas; Nebraska, May 5 (Tape 117: 1)
      - Private interviews, May 5 (Tape 117: 2)
      - Shreveport; New Orleans; Channel 3, May 6 (Tape 117: 3)
      - New Orleans, May 6 (Tape 117: 4-5)
      - Phone calls, May 10 (Tape 117: 6)
      - Idaho; US news, May 11 (Tape 117: 7)
      - Twin Falls, Idaho, May 11 (Tape 117: 8)
      - Actualities, May 11 (Tape 117: 9)
      - Boise, Idaho; Election night, May 11 (Tape 117: 10)
      - Plane Interviews; Radio Boise; Kansas City, May 12 (Tape 117: 11)
      - Kentucky, May 12-13 (Tape 117: 12)
      - Louisville; Lexington, May 13 (Tape 117: 13)
      - Kalamazoo; Cincinnati; Michigan, May 13 (Tape 117: 14)
      - Kalamazoo; Flint Michigan; May 13-14 (Tape 117: 15)
      - Flint; Detroit; Press conference; Economic Club May 14 (Tape 117: 16)
      - Detroit TV interview; May 14 (Tape 117: 17)
      - Detroit; Oklahoma; May 14-15 (Tape 117: 18)
      - On-plane interviews and LA airport; Oklahoma convention speech, May 15 (Tape 117: 19)
      - LA; Michigan primary; Reno, Las Vegas, May 18-19 (Tape 117: 20)
      - Las Vegas; Reno, May 19 (Tape 117: 21)
      - Memphis; Little Rock, May 20 (Tape 117: 22)
      - Knoxville Tennessee; TVA, May 20-21 (Tape 117: 23)
      - Nashville and Chattanooga, Tennessee, May 21 (Tape 117: 24)
      - Nashville, May 21 (Tape 117: 25)
      - Master copy: Fort Smith, Arkansas; Topeka, Arkansas convention speech, May 22 (Tape 117: 26)
      - Fort Smith, Arkansas; Topeka, Arkansas convention speech, May 22 (Tape 117: 27)
      - Oregon, May 22 (Tape 117: 28)
      - Portland, Oregon, May 22 (Tape 117: 29)
      - Portland, Oregon; Bus interviews, May 22-23 (Tape 117: 30)
      - Bus interviews; Oregon State University college speech, May 23 (Tape 117: 31)
      - Eugene, Oregon; Plane interview, LA, May 23 (Tape 117: 32)
      - LA primary night, May 25 (Tape 117: 33)
      - Orange County; Riverside press conference; May 26 (Tape 117: 34)
      - Costa Mesa, Leisure World, May 26 (Tape 117: 35)
      - San Diego arrival, Reagan, May 26-27 (Tape 117: 36)
      - San Diego, May 27 (Tape 118: 1)
      - San Diego/Las Angeles, May 27-28 (Tape 118: 2)